[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
I still remember how it begins.
You wrote
that when small animals are born
the first living creature they see
they take to be their mother
following close behind, growing attached.
In those days when you couldn't see,
I loved the way you
clung to me without holding
back, like some lost little animal,
and followed me.
But I know
we're more like parallel universes
in a movie
where the other half of us lives.
Fifteen years ago
my stepfather kept calling me
the wrong name.
I used to think
that wrong name had to be
the other half of me.
Even if fate means
I vanish from your world...
It's been fifteen years
and all I want this summer
is to see you…
Hey.
You want to sleep, go sleep somewhere else
I'm running a business here.
Aw, come on boss lady,
I'm seriously good at this.
Just give me room and board
and pay me whatever you want.
I used to work for your family
and now you want to be my waiter?
Just go back to Singapore
and be the young master.
Come on, Yong Qi
my dad cut off all my credit cards.
Do me a favor
and take me in for a bit.
Can I take that kind of responsibility?
You graduate in a few months
and you cut class to come to the mainland.
Song Yi, what are you really after?
Uh, for you, of course.
Heh heh.
Messing with me, are you?
Fine
I'm calling Mr. Song right now.
Hey!
Sis, give me a break.
If my old man finds out I'm here
he'd disown me for sure.
Song Yi, is all this really necessary?
Actually… I came here to find someone.
Find someone?
Hurry up and find them, then get going!
Hey
I don't have any leads yet.
Around here, other than me
who else do you even know?
Don't tell me you fell for a romance scam
and got conned?
Maybe I did.
I'm warning you, you'd better behave.
Right now I count as half your guardian.
So, does that mean I can stay?
Thanks, bye.
Sorry, I didn't know you…
I was just trying to help.
Did you have to react like that?
I do not need your help.
Feiyu, what are you doing here?
You okay? Are you hurt?
Hm?
Did you do this?
I didn't do anything!
It's nearly three kilometers,
how did you get here?
That's dangerous!
I'm fine.
Where's the caregiver I found for you?
She didn't come with you?
She resigned.
I'm fine on my own.
I don't need one.
You drove her off again, didn't you.
Fine.
Another spoiled prince to wait on.
Hey.
Don't look at me.
Nobody's easier to get along with.
Come on.
Go on in
I'll get the kitchen to cook.
Thank you.
Wow.
The way she treats people
it's like night and day!
He's in that condition
and you're making comparisons?
Come on.
Hey, senior.
I haven't eaten yet.
I'm starving too.
Careful now.
Feiyu.
From now on, don't come here alone.
The road's full of traffic.
It's too dangerous.
Mm.
Wait here.
What are you doing?
I... I'm waiting for my food.
I don't like sharing a table
with strangers.
Then you can go sit at another table.
Nobody's stopping you.
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
I'll move, I'll move. Happy now?
So what's the deal with you and Yong Qi?
Why's she so nice to you?
I'll introduce myself.
I'm Yong Qi's junior.
What're you two talking about?
Nothing much.
This friend of yours
wants to share my table.
Great.
Then sit together.
Feiyu, let me introduce you.
This is...
I know.
Your junior.
Mm, right. His name's Song Yi.
My junior from
National University of Singapore.
I worked part-time at
his family's Japanese restaurant.
Song Yi, this is Xu Feiyu.
His mother and I are... good friends.
Got it.
So he's my nephew.
Feiyu, I'm finding you
another caregiver today.
Don't you chase this one away too.
I've got to answer to your mother,
you know.
Do what you want.
The restaurant's about to get busy,
Song Yi.
After you eat, take Feiyu home for me.
Me!?
No, thank you.
I can get home by myself.
See? You heard him.
My nephew says
he doesn't need a ride home.
What's with everyone today?
All fighting me.
Hey— wait, wait, wait.
I'll take him, I'll take him.
I'll get him home safe, guaranteed.
If anything happens to Feiyu, it's on you.
Don't worry.
Consider it done.
Ngh—.
Feiyu, are you okay?
Song Yi, just get him home, that's all.
He doesn't like strangers touching him,
so don't.
Got it?
Fine.
Whoa! Private villa. Somebody's rich.
Easy— watch your step.
You may go now.
I brought you all this way—
and you won't even invite me in?
No.
Oh, come on—.
I walked all this way in the blazing sun,
soaked in sweat.
You won't invite me in,
at least
be a bit more polite.
Thank you for your trouble.
Please go home.
You— I— What, do I owe you something?!
Tch!
Hey.
What're you looking at?
Nothing.
Right, Yong Qi—
that Xu Feiyu guy—
is he hiring a caregiver?
Yeah.
He just had iris surgery,
and his mom's away on business in Europe,
so she asked me to find him a caregiver.
Her son has surgery and she's flying abroad.
Is she really his mother?
Don't talk nonsense.
No, no—
I'm just joking.
So can you let me give it a try?
Try what?
The caregiver job.
You?
Yeah!
Forget it, rich boy.
You're more trouble than Feiyu.
I kept a whole house full of pets
in Singapore.
Looking after one fish— shouldn't be a problem.
[TN: Feiyu's name sounds like flying fish]
Quit messing around.
Then go back to Singapore
and look after your pets.
Yong Qi.
I'm serious.
Besides, we're about the same age
we'd get along just fine.
Get along?
Yeah.
You have no idea how difficult he is.
Plus
he has haphephobia
scared of strangers touching him
and he's a total germaphobe.
What weird disease is that?
Well, no wonder.
He was never normal to begin with.
You're not normal either.
Come on.
Yong Qi.
You won't find anyone that fast anyway.
Trust me
nobody's a better fit than me.
I'll go pack right now
and start right away.
If it doesn't work
you can find someone else.
Hey… hey, Song Yi…
I'm going. It's settled.
Who is it?
Coming, one moment.
Coming, coming.
Hello, who is it?
Who is it? Hello, is anyone there?
Who is it?
Anyone there?
Hello, who is it?
Is anyone there!
Agh! Xu Feiyu.
A mousetrap at your door in broad daylight.
You psycho!
- Ow…
- You again.
Why are you at my house again?
I'm the new caregiver
Yong Qi found for you.
I already told you,
I don't need a caregiver.
Hey! Even if you don't need one
you didn't have to hurt me?
My foot hurts too much to walk.
This is assault.
So you owe me.
Owww.
Don't go in any further.
Hey.
Wait.
This is breaking and entering
I could call the police.
I politely rang the doorbell
and you opened it
so procedurally we're fine.
At most, I'm an uninvited guest.
But you? That's abusing your carer.
Ow— it hurts, it hurts.
Stop! Stop right there!
Siri! Siri, call Yong Qi.
Ohh.
Get out. Nobody let you in.
So this is the place.
(The number you have
called cannot be connected...)
In your condition, you can still do these.
Doing it blind?
Don't touch my stuff.
Get out, right now
I know you don't want a new carer
I came here to solve that problem.
Think about it.
Your mom and Yong Qi
will never let you be alone.
As long as I stay
nobody will come to bug you.
Hm?
Come on, relax
I can be invisible.
Unless you call,
I won't bother you.
Hey, ca-careful.
I'll do whatever you say,
just think about it?
Look, let me be straight with you
I ran away from home, I'm stranded
and I'm flat broke
I really do need this job.
I'm good at this stuff.
Laundry, cooking, making beds —
I'm good at all of it.
Way more than you pay for.
You can try before you buy.
You won't lose out.
Well?
Then… a three-day trial period.
A trial period?
Did you not say try before you buy?
If I am not satisfied
I can let you go at any time.
No problem!
Deal!
Tell me.
What do you need done?
I can show off right now.
Then start with the laundry I've piled up.
No problem.
Oh right! Where's the washing machine?
I don't like machine washing.
The washboard is in the bathroom.
A washboard? By hand?
What?
Can't you handle that?
I can handle it!
In Singapore
everyone washes by hand.
I'm on it.
Hey!
Careful!
I told you to call me!
What if you cut yourself on the glass?
Are you okay?
Don't touch me!
Okay!
Then don't move.
It's all broken glass here.
I just don't want you getting hurt.
From now on let me do it.
I'm not a free carer, you know.
So don't hold back.
Whoa!
What is it?
So this is what you
spent half the day on?
Not bad at all.
That's none of your business.
I'm hungry.
Perfect.
I'm hungry too.
Takeout.
I don't like takeout.
The ingredients are in the fridge.
The door is that way.
Come on.
It's just cooking.
It's my specialty.
Tell me
what do you want?
Chinese, Japanese, or Western?
It doesn't matter.
Hey.
Don't move. There's broken glass.
Let go. Who told you to touch me?
I'm your caregiver now.
On the clock, you answer to me.
Let go. Ah—.
Come here!
Let go of me!
Don't move!
Sit still.
Hey! Song Yi! I'm warning you!
If you touch me again, I'll…
You'll what?
Fire me?
Do not think you are safe
just because Yong Qi is here.
If I want you dismissed,
no one can help you.
I'm doing my job as a
caregiver. A full-time one.
How could I not touch you?
So for these three days,
you'd better get used to it.
I'll look after you like my own brother.
I'm not your damn brother.
Watch your mouth.
My mouth behaves itself.
Unlike you.
You don't mean a word.
Playing it cold.
- You'll end up with no friends.
- Understand this.
You are a temporary caregiver.
My friends are not your concern.
Xu Feiyu.
You always like this?
Like what?
Just…
scared of strangers.
You are insane! You—.
Do your job and nothing else.
We are not close. Do not cross the line.
Fine.
Then let's get close as fast as we can.
Song Yi!
Dad!
I'm only doing this for you.
Otherwise I'd pull his pants down
and beat him senseless!